用十分钟的美臀锻炼 今天会很难熬的
With great ten minute booty workout. Today is gonna burn.
这是值得的
It's gonna be worth it.
这个视频是四个拉伸挑战的一部分 可以在我的网站上找到 还有每天的健康食谱
This video is part of the four way some stretch challenge, which can find on my website, along with healthy recipes, daily.
这都是免费的 人 你所要做的就是在需要的时候加入社区的其他人
It's all free. Guys. All you need to do is to show up and join the rest of the community if need some.
热和s总是被欣赏 对我来说 大拇指一按就碎了
Hot and s always are really appreciated. It could smash at thumbs up button for me.
给我留下很多很多的灯 评论 和你的朋友分享 因为这将真正帮助我的中国
Leave me them many, many lights, comments and shared this with your friends, as it will really help my China out.
我们今天有16个练习 开始20到40秒 结束5到10秒 这种抵抗 花费了今天大多数练习的替代品 所以把它们准备在身边
We've got sixteen exercises today, twenty to the forty seconds on and five to ten seconds off. This resistance, spends alternatives for most of the exercises today, so have them ready by the side.
把所有的力量都放在地图上 我们要开始研究彩虹了
Get on all force on the map, and we're going to start to work out with rainbows.
我们 一个湖延伸到另一个湖
We, one lake extend over the other lake.
举起来再举起来 就像你在用你的腿画彩虹 如果你有一个阻力带 只要遵循替代方案 确保你使用的力量给你足够的挑战
Lifted up and over like you're drawing a rainbow with your leg. If you have a resistance band, just follow the alternatives and make sure you use a strength that gives you enough of a challenge.
还是可行的
And still doable.
哦
Oh,
你那美好的天空不允许别人休息
No rest unto the other lay engage your good skies.
嗯 从来没有
Well, never.
好 什么 伙计们 在这里休息十秒钟 我们要做一个回跳
Nice, what, guys? Ten seconds rest here, and we're going to do a kickback circle.
愉快地弯曲 然后向上踢 然后画一组 我的圆圈 当你下来 填上你的货物 因为我的肌肉连接真的很重要
Happily bent at degrees, then kick it upwards, then draw a set, my circle as you come back down, fill it in your goods as my muscle connection is really important.
我不知道
I don't know.
不要在这里休息 我们继续到另一个湖
Not taking a break here, let's move on to the other lake.
永远不会做的事
Will never do.
一个地方
A place.
在这里休息十秒钟 你可以把你的手带放在接下来的两个练习地点 在你的地图上的十字单湖蓝色桥
Ten seconds rest here, you can put your bands to the site for the next two exercises, get on your map of Cross single Lake Blue Bridge.
如果有一个 比如延长器 或把它放在你的另一边 然后用你的胶水向上推你的臀部
If one, like extender, or place it above your other side, then thrust your hips upwards using your glues.
确保你没有过度伸展你的背部 因为你不想享受你的下背部 保持你的货物和电话预约
Make sure you don't hyper extend your back as you don't want to enjoy your lower back. Keep your goods and call engaged.
现在让我们换到另一边 确保你保持 我的肌肉连接 调动你的核心和你的过剩 这个练习真的很让人感激
Now let's swap to the other side, make sure you keep that, my muscle connection, engage your core and your gluts. This exercise is really grateful.
男孩
Boys.
干得好 伙计们 他们做得很好 现在转到原力 如果你有手环 戴上 我们就开始了直接的消火栓比赛
Nice work, guys, they are doing great. Now flip around onto Old Force, put on your bands, if you have them, and we've got straightly hydrant race.
抬起你的腿 然后把它放到一边 回到中间 然后向下重复 你会感觉到盘子的一边在燃烧
Lift your legs up, then bring it to the side, back to the middle and down and repeat, you're gonna feel the burn on the side of your plate.
哦 不
Oh no.
现在让我们再走到另一个湖 专注于你的货物
Now let's walk on the other lake again, focus on your goods.
休息十秒钟 然后在训练的中途做两个直线运动 你得到这个
Ten seconds rest for your glues and were moving on two straightly circles halfway through the workout guys. You got this.
白手起家
Started up with nothing.
用你的胶水画一个合适大小的圆圈 慢慢地 慢慢地 确保你的阻力带足够强 所以
Focus on using your glues to draw a decent size circle, take it nice and slow and make sure your resistance band is strong enough, so it's.
为什么是干的
Why is it the dry.
现在我们走另一边
And now let's walk the other side.
再一次 确保你保持那9个肌肉连接
Again, make sure you keep that nine muscle connection.
他们
They.
干得好 伙计们 在这里休息十秒钟 把你们的乐队放在一边准备接下来的两个练习 我们接下来要做单腿练习
Great job, guys, ten seconds rest here, put aside your band for the next two exercises, we've got a single leg hit for next.
把你的手放在肩膀下面 一条腿伸展 一条腿弯曲 现在用胶水把你的臀部往上推
Have your hands placed below your shoulders, one leg extended and one leg bent. Now thrust your hips upwards using a glue.
确保你的核心英语是engage 而不是have
Make sure your core English are engaged and do not have.
没有休息 我们到另一边停下来吧
No rest. Let's stop to the other side.
你们做得太棒了 伙计们 我又买了些运动来给你们做蛙式打气筒
You're doing amazing, guys, just bought more exercises to go get you ready for some frog pumps.
如果他在一起打球 他会很高兴的指出来 现在冰霜的屁股向上是用了木头
Happy if he plays together and he's pointing out, now frosty hips up was using a woods.
这次的打击会有所不同 你的屁股会有这种感觉你的靴子会穿进你的身体
This is gonna hit differently. You're gonna feel this in your butt and get your boots in your core.
干得好 伙计们 桥牌打得不错 绑架是最后十秒的休息时间 我们要把它摧毁到最后
Nice work, guys, good bridge. Abductions are next final ten seconds rest, and we're going to smash it to the end.
用一只脚踢着肩膀 现在用胶水把你的臀部向外推 打开你的腿 这也会在胶水上起作用 一定要保持
Have a feet plays about shoulder with a pot, now thrust your hips outwards using a glue and open up your legs. This is going to work the site of your glue as well and make sure you keep that.
我的肌肉连接 这真的很重要
My muscle connection. It's really important.
如果你有绑带 马上把它们放下 然后翻到肚子上 我们就
Put aside those bands quickly if you have them, then flip around onto your belly, and we've got.
青蛙蛋糕 把你的腿伸直 然后在做商品的时候把腿卷起来然后稍微向上翘一下 然后再向后翘
Frog cakes, have your legs extended, and now curl them in while engaging in goods and leave those schools up a little, then back down and.
继续 几乎
Keep going well. Almost then,
最后一个练习是
And the last exercise is.
彩虹 这里没有停顿 你画的彩虹既与场地相关又与场地相关 但可能表明你在工作 那些货物 感受那灼伤
Rainbows, no break here, you're drawing rainbows with both relate to the site and back in, but may show you're engaging in working. Those goods, feel that burn.
我们完成了
Finished us.
因此 各位 我希望你们的翘臀正在燃烧
And thus the work, all, guys, I hope your booty is feeling the burn.
在评论里对给我留言吧 我们下次训练再见 Bye!
Smashed at, like put them for me and scream at me in the comments, do it, and I'll see you in the next workout. Bye,
嗯 嗯
Um, um,